Guide to the Gould family papers, 1799-[ca. 1869]
Gould family papers, 1799-[ca. 1869]
- Series VII. Microfilm
  - Diaries #2-10, 1803-1812 (Reel 2)
    Oct. 17, 1803-June 30, 1812. c. 64 ft. (1 reel pos.)
  - Diary #11, 1812-1815 (Reel 3)
    July 1, 1812-August 20, 1815. Original held by Quaker Collection, Haverford College. (1 reel pos.)
  - Diaries #12-16, 1815-1838 (Reel 4)
    August 24, 1815-Sept. 20, 1838 and Extracts from the records of the monthly meeting held by Rhode Island Quakers, 1676-1707 c. 65 ft. (1 reel pos.)
  - History of the Gould Family, 1862-1868 (Reel 5)
    History of the Gould Family from John Stanton Gould letters, volumes 1 and 2, (1 reel pos. [100 ft.])
  - History of the Gould Family, 1862-1864 (Reel 6)
    John Stanton Gould letters to Dau. Mary Gould Baldwin on the History of the Gould Family, volume 1 only, (1 reel pos. [50 ft.])
  - Diary and Genealogy, 1851-1862 (Reel 7)
    Hannah W. Gould diary, Sept. 11, 1851-Jan. 25, 1862; Gould Family genealogy chart (1 reel pos..)
  - Journal, 1847-1850 (Reel 8)
    "Journal of Residence at Albany," 1847-1850, (1 reel pos..)
  - Letter, 1718 (Reel 9)
    Sebastian Râle letter (in French), August 17, 1718, Narantsonak [Norridgewock], Maine (1 reel neg.)
  - Diary #1, 1799-1803 (Reel 10)
    Negative copy of Reel 1
  - Diaries #2-10, 1803-1812 (Reel 11)
    Negative copy of Reel 2
  - Diaries #12-16, 1815-1838 (Reel 12)
    Negative copy of Reel 4
  - History of the Gould Family, 1862-1868 (Reel 13)
    Archival master copy of Reel 5 (1 reel neg. [100 ft.])
  - History of the Gould Family, 1862-1864 (Reel 14)
    Negative copy of Reel 6 [50 ft.]
  - Diary and Genealogy, 1851-1862 (Reel 15)
    Negative copy of Reel 7
  - Journal, 1847-1850 (Reel 16)
    Negative copy of Reel 8
  - Letter, 1718 (Reel 17)
    Negative copy of Reel 9